Your Dog UP233
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Your Dog
2004 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Media Enterprises
UP233
1.0 Linear Feet
4 Digital Object(s)
4.7 Megabytes
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Media Enterprises was organized in 2002 to take over various university publications including the Tufts Health Letter, Your Dog, Catnip and Healthy Living as well as single run publications of various books.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Your Dog. It is a monthly 24-page newsletter for dog owners and enthusiasts, and is published by the Tufts Media.
- Your Dog, 2004 -- 2019; UP233.001; 1.0 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Your Dog. It is a monthly 24-page newsletter for dog owners and enthusiasts, and is published by the Tufts Media.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Your Dog, 2004-03; UP233.001.001.00001 (Volume 1)
    Volume, issue
    10, 3
    newsletters
  - Your Dog, 2004-04; UP233.001.001.00002 (Volume 1)
    10, 4
  - Your Dog, 2004-05; UP233.001.001.00003 (Volume 1)
    10, 5
  - Your Dog, 2004-06; UP233.001.001.00004 (Volume 1)
    10, 6
  - Your Dog, 2004-07; UP233.001.001.00005 (Volume 1)
    10, 7
  - Your Dog, 2004-08; UP233.001.001.00006 (Volume 1)
    10, 8
  - Your Dog, 2004-09; UP233.001.001.00007 (Volume 1)
    10, 9
  - Your Dog, 2004-11; UP233.001.001.00008 (Volume 1)
    10, 11
  - Your Dog, 2004-12; UP233.001.001.00009 (Volume 1)
    10, 12
  - Your Dog, 2005-01; UP233.001.001.00010 (Volume 1)
    11, 1
  - Your Dog, 2005-02; UP233.001.001.00011 (Volume 1)
    11, 2
  - Your Dog, 2005-03; UP233.001.001.00012 (Volume 1)
    11, 3
  - Your Dog, 2005-04; UP233.001.001.00013 (Volume 1)
    11, 4
  - Your Dog, 2005-05; UP233.001.001.00014 (Volume 1)
    11, 5
  - Your Dog, 2005-06; UP233.001.001.00015 (Volume 1)
    11, 6
  - Your Dog, 2005-07; UP233.001.001.00016 (Volume 1)
    11, 7
  - Your Dog, 2005-08; UP233.001.001.00017 (Volume 1)
    11, 8
  - Your Dog, 2005-09; UP233.001.001.00018 (Volume 1)
    11, 9
  - Your Dog, 2005-10; UP233.001.001.00019 (Volume 1)
    11, 10
  - Your Dog, 2005-11; UP233.001.001.00020 (Volume 1)
    11, 11
  - Your Dog, 2005-12; UP233.001.001.00021 (Volume 1)
    11, 12
  - Your Dog, 2006-01; UP233.001.001.00022 (Volume 1)
    12, 1
  - Your Dog, 2006-02; UP233.001.001.00023 (Volume 1)
    12, 2
  - Your Dog, 2006-03; UP233.001.001.00024 (Volume 1)
    12, 3
  - Your Dog, 2006-04; UP233.001.001.00025 (Volume 1)
    12, 4
  - Your Dog, 2006-05; UP233.001.001.00026 (Volume 1)
    12, 5
  - Your Dog, 2006-06; UP233.001.001.00027 (Volume 1)
    12, 6
  - Your Dog, 2006-07; UP233.001.001.00028 (Volume 1)
    12, 7
  - Your Dog, 2006-08; UP233.001.001.00029 (Volume 1)
    12, 8
  - Your Dog, 2006-09; UP233.001.001.00030 (Volume 1)
    12, 9
  - Your Dog, 2006-10; UP233.001.001.00031 (Volume 1)
    12, 10
  - Your Dog, 2006-11; UP233.001.001.00032 (Volume 1)
    12, 11
  - Your Dog, 2006-12; UP233.001.001.00033 (Volume 1)
    12, 12
  - Your Dog, 2007-01; UP233.001.001.00034 (Volume 1)
    13, 1
  - Your Dog, 2007-02; UP233.001.001.00035 (Volume 1)
    13, 2
  - Your Dog, 2007-03; UP233.001.001.00036 (Volume 1)
    13, 3
  - Your Dog, 2007-04; UP233.001.001.00037 (Volume 1)
    13, 4
  - Your Dog, 2007-05; UP233.001.001.00038 (Volume 1)
    13, 5
  - Your Dog, 2007-06; UP233.001.001.00039 (Volume 1)
    13, 6
  - Your Dog, 2007-07; UP233.001.001.00040 (Volume 1)
    13, 7
  - Your Dog, 2007-08; UP233.001.001.00041 (Volume 1)
    13, 8
  - Your Dog, 2007-09; UP233.001.001.00042 (Volume 1)
    13, 9
  - Your Dog, 2007-10; UP233.001.001.00043 (Volume 1)
    13, 10
  - Your Dog, 2007-11; UP233.001.001.00044 (Volume 1)
    13, 11
  - Your Dog, 2007-12; UP233.001.001.00045 (Volume 1)
    13, 12
  - Your Dog, 2008-01; UP233.001.001.00046 (Volume 1)
    14, 1
  - Your Dog, 2008-02; UP233.001.001.00047 (Volume 1)
    14, 2
  - Your Dog, 2008-03; UP233.001.001.00048 (Volume 1)
    14, 3
  - Your Dog, 2008-04; UP233.001.001.00049 (Volume 1)
    14, 4
  - Your Dog, 2008-05; UP233.001.001.00050 (Volume 1)
    14, 5
  - Your Dog, 2008-06; UP233.001.001.00051 (Volume 1)
    14, 6
  - Your Dog, 2008-07; UP233.001.001.00052 (Volume 1)
    14, 7
  - Your Dog, 2008-08; UP233.001.001.00053 (Volume 1)
    14, 8
  - Your Dog, 2008-09; UP233.001.001.00054 (Volume 1)
    14, 9
  - Your Dog, 2008-10; UP233.001.001.00055 (Volume 1)
    14, 10
  - Your Dog, 2008-11; UP233.001.001.00056 (Volume 1)
    14, 11
  - Your Dog, 2008-12; UP233.001.001.00057 (Volume 1)
    14, 12
  - Your Dog, 2009-01; UP233.001.002.00001 (Volume 2)
    15, 1
  - Your Dog, 2009-02; UP233.001.002.00002 (Volume 2)
    15, 2
  - Your Dog, 2009-03; UP233.001.002.00003 (Volume 2)
    15, 3
  - Your Dog, 2009-04; UP233.001.002.00004 (Volume 2)
    15, 4
  - Your Dog, 2009-05; UP233.001.002.00005 (Volume 2)
    15, 5
  - Your Dog, 2009-06; UP233.001.002.00006 (Volume 2)
    15, 6
  - Your Dog, 2009-07; UP233.001.002.00007 (Volume 2)
    15, 7
  - Your Dog, 2009-08; UP233.001.002.00008 (Volume 2)
    15, 8
  - Your Dog, 2009-09; UP233.001.002.00009 (Volume 2)
    15, 9
  - Your Dog, 2009-10; UP233.001.002.00010 (Volume 2)
    15, 10
  - Your Dog, 2009-11; UP233.001.002.00011 (Volume 2)
    15, 11
  - Your Dog, 2009-12; UP233.001.002.00012 (Volume 2)
    15, 12
  - Your Dog, 2010-01; UP233.001.002.00013 (Volume 2)
    16, 1
  - Your Dog, 2010-02; UP233.001.002.00014 (Volume 2)
    16, 2
  - Your Dog, 2010-03; UP233.001.002.00015 (Volume 2)
    16, 3
  - Your Dog, 2010-04; UP233.001.002.00016 (Volume 2)
    16, 4
  - Your Dog, 2010-05; UP233.001.002.00017 (Volume 2)
    16, 5
  - Your Dog, 2010-06; UP233.001.002.00018 (Volume 2)
    16, 6
  - Your Dog, 2010-07; UP233.001.002.00019 (Volume 2)
    16, 7
  - Your Dog, 2010-08; UP233.001.002.00020 (Volume 2)
    16, 8
  - Your Dog, 2010-09; UP233.001.002.00021 (Volume 2)
    16, 9
  - Your Dog, 2010-10; UP233.001.002.00022 (Volume 2)
    16, 10
  - Your Dog, 2010-11; UP233.001.002.00023 (Volume 2)
    16, 11
  - Your Dog, 2010-12; UP233.001.002.00024 (Volume 2)
    16, 12
  - Your Dog, 2011-01; UP233.001.002.00025 (Volume 2)
    17, 1
  - Your Dog, 2011-02; UP233.001.002.00026 (Volume 2)
    17, 2
  - Your Dog, 2011-03; UP233.001.002.00027 (Volume 2)
    17, 3
  - Your Dog, 2011-04; UP233.001.002.00028 (Volume 2)
    17, 4
  - Your Dog, 2011-05; UP233.001.002.00029 (Volume 2)
    17, 5
  - Your Dog, 2011-06; UP233.001.002.00030 (Volume 2)
    17, 6
  - Your Dog, 2011-07; UP233.001.002.00031 (Volume 2)
    17, 7
  - Your Dog, 2011-08; UP233.001.002.00032 (Volume 2)
    17, 8
  - Your Dog, 2011-09; UP233.001.002.00033 (Volume 2)
    17, 9
  - Your Dog, 2011-10; UP233.001.002.00034 (Volume 2)
    17, 10
  - Your Dog, 2011-11; UP233.001.002.00035 (Volume 2)
    17, 11
  - Your Dog, 2011-12; UP233.001.002.00036 (Volume 2)
    17, 12
  - Your Dog, 2012-01; UP233.001.002.00037 (Volume 2)
    18, 1
  - Your Dog, 2012-02; UP233.001.002.00038 (Volume 2)
    18, 2
  - Your Dog, 2012-03; UP233.001.002.00039 (Volume 2)
    18, 3
  - Your Dog, 2012-04; UP233.001.002.00040 (Volume 2)
    18, 4
  - Your Dog, 2012-05; UP233.001.002.00041 (Volume 2)
    18, 5
  - Your Dog, 2012-06; UP233.001.002.00042 (Volume 2)
    18, 6
  - Your Dog, 2012-07; UP233.001.002.00043 (Volume 2)
    18, 7
  - Your Dog, 2012-08; UP233.001.002.00044 (Volume 2)
    18, 8
  - Your Dog, 2012-09; UP233.001.002.00045 (Volume 2)
    18, 9
  - Your Dog, 2012-10; UP233.001.002.00046 (Volume 2)
    18, 10
  - Your Dog, 2012-11; UP233.001.002.00047 (Volume 2)
    18, 11
  - Your Dog, 2012-12; UP233.001.002.00048 (Volume 2)
    18, 12
  - Your Dog, 2013-01; UP233.001.002.00049 (Volume 2)
    19, 1
  - Your Dog, 2013-02; UP233.001.002.00050 (Volume 2)
    19, 2
  - Your Dog, 2013-03; UP233.001.002.00051 (Volume 2)
    19, 3
  - Your Dog, 2013-09; UP233.001.002.00052 (Volume 2)
    XIX, 9
  - Your Dog, 2014-05; UP233.001.002.00053 (Volume 2)
    XX, 5
  - Your Dog, 2015-08; UP233.001.002.00054.000001 (Volume 2)
    XXI, 8
  - Your Dog, 2016-06; UP233.001.002.00054.000002 (Volume 2, Folder 54)
    XXII, 6
  - Your Dog, 2019-01; UP233.001.002.00055 (Volume 2)
    Volume, Issue
    XXV, 1